Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5 1870-2017
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5
- Union Democracy, Association for, 1998; Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Item 5: Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Item 6: Annual Performace Appraisal, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
    By Union Carbide. Form. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Perspectives: On Crticial Public Policy Issues, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
    By Union Carbide. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Perspectives: On Central Public Policy Issues, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
    By Union Carbide. The Business of Black America. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Perspectives: On Critical Public Policy Issues, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
    By Union Carbide. Starting Over, Again: Rethinking U.S. Water Quality Programs. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Perspectives: On Central Public Policy Issues, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
    By Union Carbide. Resources and Responsibility. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Perspectives: On Central Public Policy Issues, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
    By Union Carbide. How to Stop Talking About Industrial Wastes and Do Something About Them. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Perspectives: On Central Public Policy Issues, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
    By Union Carbide. Industrial Development's New Dimension. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Perspectives: On Central Public Policy Issues, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
    By Union Carbide. Strategic Competitveness. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Perspectives: On Central Public Policy Issues, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
    By Union Carbide. Planning for Energy Emergencies. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Perspectives: On Central Public Policy Issues, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
    By Union Carbide. A Petrochemical Perspective. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Perspectives: On Central Public Policy Issues, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
    By Union Carbide. Chemicals From Petroleum. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Plans and Policies, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
    By Union Carbide. A Worksheet for I.A.s. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Making the most of..Your International Assignment, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Item 19: Product Directory 1981, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Item 20: Electronic Division Profile, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
    By Union Carbide. October 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: UCC Gets Good Reviews, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
    By Union Carbide. Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: HQNews, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Item 23: Union Carbide, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Item 24: Public Policy Agenda 1984, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
    By Union Carbide. Informational Pamphlet. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Union Carbide Chemicals and Plastics, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Item 26: We Exist For Our Customers, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Item 27: Corporate Placement Service, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
    By Union Carbide. Internal/External Job Search Workbook. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Special Report, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
    By Union Carbide. News Booklet. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: You and Union Carbide: A Strong Partnership, Publication (Box 29, Folder 22)
- Union Labor Life Insurance Company, Publication (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Ulico Casualty Company, Publication (Box 30, Folder 1)
    By Union labor Life Insurance Co. 1990 Annual Report. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: 1990 Annual Report, Publication (Box 30, Folder 1)
    By Union labor Life Insurance Co. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: 1989 Annual Report, Publication (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: 1988 Annual Report, Publication (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: 1989 Annual Report, Publication (Box 30, Folder 1)
    By Union labor Life Insurance Co. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: WDL News, Publication (Box 30, Folder 1)
    By Workers Defense League. Newsletter - Spring 1991. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Bulletin, Publication (Box 30, Folder 1)
    By Ullico. Number 2, 1991. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Bulletin, Publication (Box 30, Folder 1)
    By Ullico. November 2, 1991. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Bulletin, Publication (Box 30, Folder 1)
    By Ullico. August 1992. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Bulletin, Publication (Box 30, Folder 1)
    By Ullico. August, 1992 - Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Bulletin, Publication (Box 30, Folder 1)
    By Ullico. December, 1992. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Bulletin, Publication (Box 30, Folder 1)
    By Ullico. December, 1992 - Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: News Release, Publication (Box 30, Folder 1)
    By Union labor Life Insurance Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: News Release, Publication (Box 30, Folder 1)
    By Union labor Life Insurance Company. December 21, 1999. Item is in English.
- United Labor Service Agency, Publication (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: United Labor Service Agency, Publication (Box 30, Folder 2)
    By United Labor Service Agency. Informational Pamphlet. Item is in English.
- Uniroyal, Inc. - Handbooks, manuals, etc., Publication (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: 1980 Directory of Products and Services, Publication (Box 30, Folder 3)
    By Uniroyal. Item is in English.
- Union Pacific Corporation - EAP Activity Report, 1972-1986; Publication (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Activity Report: 1972-1986, Publication (Box 30, Folder 4)
    By Union Pacific Corporation. Item is in English.
- UNISYS Infor, Publication (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: INFO, Publication (Box 30, Folder 5)
    By Unisys Corporation. Newspaper - March, 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: INFO, Publication (Box 30, Folder 5)
    By Unisys Corporation. Newspaper - January, 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: INFO, Publication (Box 30, Folder 5)
    By Unisys Corporation. Newspaper - January, 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: INFO, Publication (Box 30, Folder 5)
    By Unisys Corporation. Newspaper - Number 3, May, 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: INFO, Publication (Box 30, Folder 5)
    By Unisys Corporation. Newspaper - June, 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: INFO, Publication (Box 30, Folder 5)
    By Unisys Corporation. Newspaper - October 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: INFO, Publication (Box 30, Folder 5)
    By Unisys Corporation. Newspaper - November, 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: INFO, Publication (Box 30, Folder 5)
    By Unisys Corporation. Newspaper - December, 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: INFO, Publication (Box 30, Folder 5)
    By Unisys Corporation. Newspaper - May, 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: INFO, Publication (Box 30, Folder 5)
    By Unisys Corporation. Newspaper - August 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: INFO, Publication (Box 30, Folder 5)
    By Unisys Corporation. Newspaper - No. 5 - Oct./Nov. 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: INFO, Publication (Box 30, Folder 5)
    By Unisys Corporation. Newspaper - January, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: INFO, Publication (Box 30, Folder 5)
    By Unisys Corporation. Newspaper - Feburary, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: INFO, Publication (Box 30, Folder 5)
    By Unisys Corporation. Newspaper - July, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: INFO, Publication (Box 30, Folder 5)
    By Unisys Corporation. Newspaper - April, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: INFO, Publication (Box 30, Folder 5)
    By Unisys Corporation. Newspaper - November, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: INFO, Publication (Box 30, Folder 5)
    By Unisys Corporation. Newspaper - December, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: INFO, Publication (Box 30, Folder 5)
    By Unisys Corporation. Newspaper - No. 1 - March, 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: INFO, Publication (Box 30, Folder 5)
    By Unisys Corporation. Newspaper - July, 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: INFO, Publication (Box 30, Folder 5)
    By Unisys Corporation. Newspaper - September, 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: INFO, Publication (Box 30, Folder 5)
    By Unisys Corporation. Newspaper - No.4, November, 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: INFO, Publication (Box 30, Folder 5)
    By Unisys Corporation. Newspaper - No. 4, Feburary 1991. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: INFO, Publication (Box 30, Folder 5)
    By Unisys Corporation. Newspaper - Vol.6, No. 2, June 1991. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: INFO, Publication (Box 30, Folder 5)
    By Unisys Corporation. Newspaper -Vol. 6, No. 3, August 1991. Item is in English.
- United Brands Company - Handbooks, manuals, etc., Publication (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: New York Office Employee Handbook, Publication (Box 30, Folder 6)
    By United Brands. Febuary 1984. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: United Brands and Costa Rica- A closer look, Publication (Box 30, Folder 6)
    By United Brands. Newsletter - May 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: United Brands and Panama- A closer look, Publication (Box 30, Folder 6)
    By United Brands. Newsletter - July 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: United Brands and Honduras- A closer look, Publication (Box 30, Folder 6)
    By United Brands. Newsletter - June 1981. Item is in English.
- United States. Air Force. Saratoga Air Force Station, Publication (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Intinerary Card for an event, Publication (Box 30, Folder 7)
    By United States Airforce Saratoga Airforce Station. Dining Out - 18 March 1972. Item is in English.
- United States. Commission on Civil Rights, Publication (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Political Activity of Federal Officers and Employees, Publication (Box 30, Folder 8)
    By U.S. Civil Service Commission. Pamphlet 66. Item is in English.
- United States. Congress. Office of Technology Assessment, Publication (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Employee Handbook, Publication (Box 30, Folder 9)
    By United States Commission on Civil Rights. September 1980. Item is in English.
- United States Dept. of the Army, Publication (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Plant Closing: Advance Notice and Rapid Response, Publication (Box 30, Folder 10)
    By United States Congress. Office of Technology Assessment. September 1986. Item is in English.
- U.S. Department of Commerce - Handbooks, manuals, etc., Publication (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Employee Services and Quality of Worklife, Publication (Box 30, Folder 11)
    By U.S. Dept. of the Army. February 1984. Item is in English.
- DOL, Publication (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Statement of the Chamber of Commerce of the United States, Publication (Box 30, Folder 12)
    By U.S. Department of Commerce. February 3, 1981 - By: Eric J. Oxfeld. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: A Simple Exterior Can Contain Suprising Things, Publication (Box 30, Folder 12)
    By U.S. Department of Commerce. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Performance Plan, Progress Review & Appraisal Record, Publication (Box 30, Folder 12)
    By U.S. Department of Commerce. Form. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: A Simple Exterior Can Contain Suprising Things, Publication (Box 30, Folder 12)
    By U.S. Department of Commerce. Informational Booklet. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Employee Handbook, Publication (Box 30, Folder 12)
    By U.S. Department of Commerce. November, 1984. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Emergency and Permanent Policies of Spreading Work in Industrial Employment, Publication (Box 30, Folder 12)
    By The President's Emergency Committee. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: A Manager's Guide to Taking Adverse Actions, Publication (Box 30, Folder 12)
    By U.S. Department of Commerce. June 1984. Item is in English.
- United States. Dept. of Labor, Publication (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Wartime Reminders to Women Who Work, Publication (Box 30, Folder 13)
    By U.S. Department of Labor. January 1943. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Workmen's Compensation: The Benefits, Publication (Box 30, Folder 13)
    By U.S. Department of Labor. Informational Booklet. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Foreman's Guide to Labor Relations, Publication (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: The Women's Bureau of the U.S. Department of Labor, Publication (Box 30, Folder 13)
    By U.S. Department of Labor. August 1941. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Collecting Back Wages, Publication (Box 30, Folder 13)
    By U.S. Department of Labor. Informational Pamphlet. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Why Legislate Living Wages for Women Workers?, Publication (Box 30, Folder 13)
    By U.S. Department of Labor. Informational Pamphlet - March 15, 1935. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Union Provisions for Maternity Leave for Women Members, Publication (Box 30, Folder 13)
    By U.S. Department of Labor. No.3 - Union Series. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Your State Department of Labor, Publication (Box 30, Folder 13)
    By U.S. Department of Labor. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Women in Brazil Today, Publication (Box 30, Folder 13)
    By Msry M. Cannon. Informational Pamphlet. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Worker's Stake in Safety, Publication (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Item 11: Minimum Quantity Budget, Publication (Box 30, Folder 13)
    By U.S. Department of Labor. Informtional Pamphlet. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Summary of Activities of the Farm Labor Divison United States Empolyment Service 1930, Publication (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Item 13: Wages of Office Workers 1940, Publication (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Item 14: What You Don't Want in an "Equal Pay" Bill, Publication (Box 30, Folder 13)
    By Women's Bureau U.S. Department of Labor. December 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: The Women's Bureau of the U.S. Department of Labor, Publication (Box 30, Folder 13)
    By U.S. Department of Labor. Informational Pamphlet - July 1939. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Silicosis Prevention: Dust Control in Foundries, Publication (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Item 17: Workmen's Compensation: The Benefits, Publication (Box 30, Folder 13)
    By U.S. Department of Labor. February 1939 - Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: A Supervisor's Guide For Staffing Positions, Publication (Box 30, Folder 13)
    By U.S. Department of Labor. August 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Women's Bureau: Meeting the Challenges of the 80's, Publication (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Item 20: Facts on U.S. Working Women, Publication (Box 30, Folder 13)
    By U.S. Department of Labor. July 1985. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: History of the Women's Bureau: 1920-1985, Publication (Box 30, Folder 13)
    By U.S. Department of Labor. January 1985. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Child Care Centers Sponsored by Employers and Labor Unions in the United States, Publication (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Item 23: Friends of the Department of Labor Report, Publication (Box 30, Folder 13)
    By U.S. Department of Labor. No.2, Fall 1988. Item is in English.
- DOL, Publication (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: What Work Requires of Schools: A Scans Report for America 2000, Publication (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: Labor Hall of Fame: Celebrating the American Worker-Growth and Change in a Free Society, Publication (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: Labor Hall of Fame, Publication (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Item 4: DOL Academy Course Catalog, Publication (Box 30, Folder 14)
    By U.S. Department of Labor. Book. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Brief History of the American Labor Movement, Publication (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Item 6: A Supervisor's Guide For Performance Management, Publication (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Item 7: Performance Standards and Appraisal for Employees in the Local 12 Bargaining Units, Publication (Box 30, Folder 14)
    By U.S. Department of Labor. Form - August 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: DOL Workplace 2000, Publication (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Item 9: Employee Handbook, Publication (Box 30, Folder 14)
- United States. Dept. of Labor, Publication (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: The Informal Sector in Mexico, Publication (Box 30, Folder 15)
    By U.S. Department of Labor. September 1992. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Description of the Proposed North American Free Trade Agreement, Publication (Box 30, Folder 15)
    By The Governments of Canada, The United Mexican States and The United States of America. August 12, 1992. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: North American Agreement on Labor Corporation Annual Report, Publication (Box 30, Folder 15)
    By U.S. Department of Labor. January 1995. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: NAFTA, Collective Bargaining, and Employment Adjustments in the United States and Canada: Implications for Michigan, Publication (Box 30, Folder 15)
    By Richard N. Block. February 1996. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The North American Agreement on Labor Corporation an Assessment of its First Year's Implementation, Publication (Box 30, Folder 15)
    By Joaquin Otero. Article. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Summary of Environmental Provisions, Publication (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Item 7: 1994 U.S.- Mexico Trade Data: Nafta Impacts, Publication (Box 30, Folder 15)
    By The Staff of the Joint Economic Committee. Staff Study - November 1994. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Daily Report for Excecutives Regulation, Economics and Law Text, Publication (Box 30, Folder 15)
    By U.S. Department of Labor. September 13, 1993. Item is in English.
- United States. Dept. of Labor and Department of Education, Publication (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: What Works: Workplaces Without Drugs, Publication (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: An Employer's Guide to Dealing With Substance Abuse, Publication (Box 30, Folder 16)
    By U.S. Department of Labor. October 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: What Works: Workplaces Without Alcohol and Other Drugs, Publication (Box 30, Folder 16)
- Western Airlines, Publication (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: The Bottom Line: Basic Skills in the Workplace, Publication (Box 30, Folder 17)
    By U.S. Department of Labor and U.S Department of Education. Informational Booklet. Item is in English.
- United States. Dept. of Labor - Employee Handbook, 1971-1972; Publication (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Western Airlines and Its Four Major Unions, Publication (Box 30, Folder 18)
    By Western Airlines. Item is in English.
- United States. Dept. of Labor-Bureau of International Labor Affairs, Publication (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Employee Handbook, Publication (Box 30, Folder 19)
    By U.S. Department of Labor. September 1971. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Unemployment Insurance Claims, Publication (Box 30, Folder 19)
    By U.S. Department of Labor. December 2, 1999. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Unemployment Insurance Claims, Publication (Box 30, Folder 19)
    By U.S. Department of Labor. November 24, 1999. Item is in English.
- United States. Dept. of Labor. Bureau of Labor-Management Relations and Cooperative Programs, Publication (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: The Role of the U.S. Department of Labor in Foreign Affairs, Publication (Box 30, Folder 20)
    By U.S. Department of Labor - Bureau of International Labor Affairs. February 1960. Item is in English.
- United States. Dept. of Labor - Bureau of Labor Standards, Publication (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Plant Closing Checklist: A Guide to Best Practice, Publication (Box 30, Folder 21)
    By U.S. Department of Labor - Bureau of Labor-Management Relations. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Preventing Layoffs, Publication (Box 30, Folder 21)
- United States. Dept. of Labor. Bureau of Labor Statistics, Publication (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: We're never too young to learn Safety, Publication (Box 30, Folder 22)
    By U.S. Department of Labor - Bureau of Labor Standards. Informational Pamphlet. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Workers' Savings and Income in 1945, Publication (Box 30, Folder 22)
- United States. Dept. of Labor. Employment and Training Administration, Publication (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Substance Abuse Provisions in Employee Benefit Plans, Publication (Box 30, Folder 23)
    By U.S. Department of Labor - Bureau of Labor Standards. August 1992. Item is in English.
- United States. Dept. of Labor. - Glass Ceiling Commission, Publication (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Work-Based Learning: Training America's Workers, Publication (Box 30, Folder 24)
    By U.S. Department of Labor - Employment and Training Administration. November 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Tips For Finding the Right Job, Publication (Box 30, Folder 24)
    By U.S. Department of Labor - Employment and Training Administration. Informational Booklet. Item is in English.
- United States. Dept. of Labor. - Glass Ceiling Commission, Publication (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Glass Ceiling Report: Let the Barriers Tumble Down, Publication (Box 30, Folder 25)
    By U.S. Department of Labor - Glass Ceiling Commission. July/August 1993. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Cracking the Glass Ceiling, Publication (Box 30, Folder 25)
    By Jonathan Claw. Article - April 1994. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: " The Impact of Corporate Restructuring and Downsizing on the Managerial Careers of Minorites and Women, Publication (Box 30, Folder 25)
    By Linda F. White. Letter - November 15, 1994. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Researchers Selected for Glass Ceiling Commission projects, Publication (Box 30, Folder 25)
    By U.S. Department of Labor - Glass Ceiling Commission. List - Februrary 16, 1994. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Special Report: Floor to Ceiling, Publication (Box 30, Folder 25)
    By Diana Kunde. December 3, 1993 - Article. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Summary of Glass Ceiling Hearing, Kansas City, KS, Publication (Box 30, Folder 25)
    By U.S. Department of Labor - Glass Ceiling Commission. December 2, 1992. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Summary of Glass Ceiling Commission Meeting Washington, D.C., Publication (Box 30, Folder 25)
    By U.S. Department of Labor - Glass Ceiling Commission. June 25, 1993. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: BNA's Daily Labor Reporter System - Daily Labor Report, Publication (Box 30, Folder 25)
    By U.S. Department of Labor - Glass Ceiling Commission. December 22, 1993. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Summary of Glass Ceiling Commission Hearing Dallas, Texas, Publication (Box 30, Folder 25)
    By U.S. Department of Labor - Glass Ceiling Commission. December 10, 1993. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Title II - Glass Ceiling, Publication (Box 30, Folder 25)
    By U.S. Department of Labor - Glass Ceiling Commission. November 21, 1991. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Research Available From The Glass Ceiling Commission, Publication (Box 30, Folder 25)
    By U.S. Department of Labor - Glass Ceiling Commission. October 13, 1994. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Breaking the Glass Ceiling, Publication (Box 30, Folder 25)
    By U.S. Department of Labor - Glass Ceiling Commission. Informational Pamphlet. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Summary of Glass Ceiling Commission Hearing Los Angeles, California, Publication (Box 30, Folder 25)
    By U.S. Department of Labor - Glass Ceiling Commission. February 11, 1994. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Use of Enforcement Techniques in Eliminating, Publication (Box 30, Folder 25)
    By Jonathan S. Leonard. April 1994 - Report. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: An Examination of the Impact of Family-Friendly Policies on the Glass Ceiling, Publication (Box 30, Folder 25)
    By U.S. Department of Labor - Glass Ceiling Commission. Final Report - January 1994. Item is in English.
- United States. Dept. of Labor. - Glass Ceiling Commission, Publication (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Barriers to Workplace Advancement Experienced by Women in Low-Paying Occupations, Publication (Box 30, Folder 26)